// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: " Who invented Java Programming?",
        answer: "James Gosling",
        options: [
          "Guido van Rossum",
          "James Gosling",
          "Dennis Ritchie",
           "Bjarne Stroustrup"
        ]
    },

    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which package contains the Random class?",
    answer: "java.util package",
    options: [
      "java.util package",
      "ava.lang package",
      "java.awt package",
      "java.io package"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which keyword is used for accessing the features of a package?",
    answer: "import",
    options: [
      "package",
      "import",
      "extends",
      "export"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "How many threads can be executed at a time?",
    answer: "Multiple threads",
    options: [
      "Only one thread",
      "Multiple threads",
      "Only main (main() method) thread",
      "Two threads"
    ]
  },
   
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " Which one of the following is not a Java feature?",
    answer: "Use of pointers",
    options: [
      "Object-oriented",
      "Use of pointers",
      "Portable",
      "Dynamic and Extensible"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the extension of java code files?",
    answer: ".java",
    options: [
      ".js",
      ".txt",
      ".class",
      ".java"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following is not a segment of memory in java?",
    answer: "Register Segment",
    options: [
      "Code Segment",
      "Register Segment",
      "Stack Segment",
      "Heap Segment"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of these are selection statements in Java?",
    answer: "if()",
    options: [
      "break",
      "continue",
      "for()",
      "if()"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of these keywords can be used to prevent Method overriding in Java?",
    answer: "final",
    options: [
      "final",
      "protected",
      "statict",
      "constant"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of these keywords are used for the block to be examined for exceptions?",
    answer: "try",
    options: [
      "check",
      "throw",
      "catch",
      "try"
    ]
  },

  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];